weddepot.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy - WedDepot.com

Please read this Privacy Policy (this "Policy") carefully before using WedDepot.com (the "Website"). By accessing, browsing and using the Website, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Policy. This Policy applies for your use of the Website only; should you follow a link on the Website to another website, you are no longer covered by this Policy. 

**Privacy Policy:**

WedDepot.com reserves the right to make changes to any part of this Policy in its sole discretion, at any time and without prior notice. Continued use of the Website following any such change will constitute acceptance of such changes. 

WedDepot.com respects your privacy. Across our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your requests, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the WedDepot.com family of companies with your consent or with companies that help WedDepot.com fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share WedDepot.com's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact WedDepot.com with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the data you have given us and request correction or deletion. Our goal is to ensure the highest levels of security and confidentiality. 

A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT PERSONS UNDER AGE 18. Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use any services on the Website 

OTHER LIMITATIONS. While WedDepot.com takes reasonable steps to safeguard and to prevent unauthorized access to your information, WedDepot.com cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and WedDepot.com makes no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that WedDepot.com will prevent unauthorized access to your private information. IN NO EVENT SHALL WedDepot.com BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES (WHETHER CONSEQUENTIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR OTHERWISE) ARISING OUT OF, OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH, A THIRD PARTY'S UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARE BASED ON CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, TORT OR OTHER THEORIES OF LIABILITY, AND ALSO REGARDLESS OF WHETHER WedDepot.com WAS GIVEN ACTUAL OR CONSTRUCTIVE NOTICE THAT DAMAGES WERE POSSIBLE. 

INTERNATIONAL USERS-APPLICABLE LAW. WedDepot.com collects, processes, stores, discloses and disposes of personal information that you submit to us in accordance with applicable United States law. Please note that the personal information you submit to WedDepot.com will be transferred to the United States to be processed by WedDepot.com in order to provide the Website and its services to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Policy. If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that WedDepot.com may collect and use your personal information, as discussed in this Policy, outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, WedDepot.com may store such personal information in the United States, outside your resident jurisdiction. Please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for personal information than may be available in your country. 

**Privacy and Data Security**

At WedDepot.com, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit WedDepot.com.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site (www.WedDepot.com) or when you use our online support offerings. Other WedDepot.com and WedDepot.com Co-branded sites may operate under their own privacy and security policies. Visit www.nclnet.org/essentials to learn more about how to protect your privacy on the Internet through a consumer education campaign called Online E-ssentials. 

**WedDepot.com only asks for specific types of personal information**

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate. 

For example, we request information from you when you: 

* Register on WedDepot.com.com 
* Request informaiton from vendors 
* Place an order on our store 
* Provide feedback in an online "TALK" message board 
* communicate with vendors in our PMB 
* Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer 
* Request e-mail notification of your order status 
* Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list 
* Fill out a support request 
* Choose interests 

In each of the instances above, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information, customer number and service tag number, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.

**WedDepot.com only uses your personal information for specific purposes**

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with WedDepot.com. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on WedDepot.com.com and alert you to service upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from WedDepot.com. Agents or contractors of WedDepot.com who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for WedDepot.com. WedDepot.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

**You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from WedDepot.com at any time**

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only WedDepot.com (or agents working on behalf of WedDepot.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information.

**WedDepot.com will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent**

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of WedDepot.com for the purpose of performing services for WedDepot.com.

**Internet Commerce**

The online store at WedDepot.com.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. WedDepot.com is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may place an order without credit card information and a representative will contact you. Alternatively, you may always contact a sales representative over the telephone. Simply call . It has always been a WedDepot.com practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.

**Customized Experience**

New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At WedDepot.com, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.WedDepot.com. WedDepot.com has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the WedDepot.com.com site.

**Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to WedDepot.com.com are not covered by this privacy statement. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, WedDepot.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Children's Privacy**

WedDepot.com takes children's privacy seriously. WedDepot.com does not seek to collect personal information about children through its Web site. Like other operators of Web sites for children, WedDepot.com is prohibited by law from conditioning a child's participation in an activity disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. If a child submits information to us through any part of our Web site and we know that the person submitting the information is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete such information that we collect inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. In the odd event that a parent requests review or deletion of information about a kid before we have discovered and deleted the information, then we will of course honor that request.

**Other Web sites**

WedDepot.com's Web sites contain links to other Web sites that are not operated by WedDepot.com. WedDepot.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate. Some parts of the Web site are animated using downloadable applications with Macromedia's Shockwave/Flash.

**Contact WedDepot.com**

WedDepot.com is the sole operator of the WedDepot.com Web sites. If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please call or email us at the following address:

**support@WedDepot.com**

WedDepot.com wants to help you keep your personal information accurate 

You can request the individual information that WedDepot.com has collected by submitting a request.

Effective Date: 07/01/07
